(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T08:28:33.521121",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together!
Lifetime showtime anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright!
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
Bau bau bau bau!
My heart 'n' soul 'n' tail are FUWAWA!
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away!
Just call for me, we're only a bark away!
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe!
Fuwa! Moco! Fuwa! Moco!
I love being tricky!
Doggy kisses are for me!
I love lots of walkies!
Don't need no leashes for me!
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere!
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you!
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together!
Lifetime showtime anytime bau bau!
一緒に行こう guys! Sing with you!
Let's go, guys! Sing with you!
Stars wink Moon spotlight furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together!
Lifetime showtime anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright!
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Bau! Woooo... Bau! Woooo...
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell.
Holding back, doggy-dog kept sealed away, bau!
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz, we're meant to be free!
it's showtime！
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
Wanna be together!
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau！
Anytime, bau bau!
yeah, future is bright
(yeah 二人は)
(Yeah, together we are)
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters！
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
fuwa！moco！
Fuwa! Moco!
(bau bau bau bau！)
(Bau bau, bau bau!)
心も体もfuwawaで
My heart 'n soul 'n tail are fuwawa,
気持ちごと浮くことあるだけど
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away.
吠えれば魔界の番犬で
Just call for me, we're only a bark away,
あなたの笑顔を守りたいよ
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe.
fuwa！moco！
Fuwa! Moco!
いたずら大好き
I love being tricky,
ペロペロもスキ
Doggy kisses are for me.
おさんぽ大好き
I love lots of walkies,
リードはいらない
Don't need no leashes for me.
どこでもmococoついていくから
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere,
fuwa mocoどっちも連れていって二人で吠えられる
Fuwamoco together, take us along with you,
it's showtime！
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい(oh！)
Wanna be together (Oh!)
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau！
Anytime, bau bau!
一生涯
Forever and ever,
sing with you
stars wink
moon spotlight
furr-ever glow
it's showtime！
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
Wanna be together!
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau！
Anytime, bau bau!
yeah, future is bright
(yeah 二人は)
(Yeah, together we are)
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters！
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
bau！woooo…
Bau! Woooo...
bau！
Bau!
昔々檻の中で
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell,
わくわくドキドキ抑えられ
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away,
bau！
Bau!
爆発しそうになっちゃって大脱出 it's play time
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free!
ゴール目指して
Make a break for it,
足は止まらない
It's playtime!
笑顔一番でも
Paws hitting the pavement,
くしゃみとまらない
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes.
今だまだ怯えだけれど
Gonna keep you smilin',
二人の絆は強いから
But my sneezes won't stop flyin' by.
絶対壊さないだから
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs,
いつだって
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable,
it's that day! (today！)
We're a pair unbreakable!
lifetime！showtime！
And that's why,
not tomorrow！bau bau！
Always,
一生涯
It's that day! (Today!)
walk with you！
Lifetime! Showtime!
good times and
Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
bad times
Forever and ever,
it doesn't matter！
Walk with you!
いつだって
Good times and bad times,
it's that day！
It doesn't matter!
lifetime showtime
Always,
everyday！bau bau！
It's that day!
yeah, 二人は
Lifetime showtime, everyday! Bau bau!
happy lucky puppy sisters
Yeah, together we are
fuwamoco bau bau！
Happy lucky puppy sisters,
everybody, bau bau！
Fuwamoco bau bau!
hallo hallo bau bau！
Everybody, bau bau!
everybody, bau bau！
Hallo hallo bau bau!
ダメダメ ノンノン！
Everybody, bau bau!
don't touch the ears！
Bad-bad, no, no!
もふもふ ノンノン！
Don't touch the ears!
don't touch the tail！
Fluffy-wuffy, no, no!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！bau！
Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！モココだよ！bau！
I'm not a chiwawa, I'm Fuwawa, bau!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ bau！
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo, bau!
and together, we're
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! Bau!
fuwamoco！
And together, we're
二人分の夢を掛け合わせたら
Fuwamoco!
目が覚めてしまうほど無限大になってしまう
Gather up our dreams,
たくさんあって叶え切れないかもだけど
And suddenly you'll come to realize,
ずっとチャレンジできる
There's as many as there are stars,
一緒だから
Illuminating the night sky.
it's showtime
Never-ending dreams,
一緒にいたい fufu！
We don't know if they all can be achieved,
it's showtime
But we'll keep on going furr-ever,
一緒にいたい fufu！
Together here with you!
it's showtime
一緒にいたいよ
Wanna be together (Fufu!)
ふわふわ
It's showtime!
もこもこ
Wanna be together (Fufu!)
包まれて
It's showtime!
君の笑顔は守りたいよ
Wanna be together,
一番の願い
Fuwa fuwa, moco moco,
it's showtime！
Hand in hand with you!
一緒にいたい(oh！)
Bring your smile, rain or shine,
lifetime showtime
We'll protect it,
anytime bau bau！
Won't forget our pledge to you!
一生涯
It's showtime!
sing with you
Wanna be together (Oh!)
stars wink
Lifetime showtime!
moon spotlight
Anytime, bau bau!
furr-ever glow
Forever and ever,
it's showtime！
Sing with you!
一緒にいたいよ
Stars wink,
lifetime showtime
Moon spotlight,
anytime bau bau！
Furr-ever glow!
and together, we're
It's showtime!
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters！
Wanna be together!
fuwa！moco！
Lifetime showtime!
Anytime, bau bau!
fuwa！moco！
And together, we're
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
fuwa！moco！
Fuwa! Moco!
fuwamoco (bau bau)
わちゃわちゃ！
Wachawacha!
おーまい！
Oh, my!
ようこそお前！
Welcome to our
FUWAMOCO Wacha☆Wacha Birthday Festival!
Fuwamoco Wachawacha Birthday Festival!
やったー！bau bau！
Yay! Bau bau!
ありがとうございます！お祝いに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate!
フワワでーす！
I'm F-Fuwawa!
モココでーす！
And I'm Mococo!
今日はストリーミングライブに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to our stream live today!
Thank you!
Well, to continue off from yesterday's Friday Show, SunaNagi's...
today we have...
A big guest! Yay!
Can you believe it? It's already been three years, right?
Our third birthday in Hololive!
Ah, but Mococo-chan, we can't forget that really important thing, right?
Huh?
Introductions!
Ah! Okay!
I'm not a chihuahua!
I am Fuwawa!
I know, Fuwawa!
I'm Mococo!
We are Hololive English Advent twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together, we are...
Fuwamoco!
Bau bau!
We have an amazing birthday festival stage here!
Amazing stage!
Bau bau!
And such a big Blue Sky too!
Three, two, one, bau bau!
It's so big and wide too!
Thank you for being here with us today!
Singing and dancing today is not just going to be us, right?
No, we're also here with some very special guests too!
So please look forward to it and make it fun!
And another mysterious guest too? Who could it be?
A birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Something really important!
I think you know well, right?
Hashtag! Yes, the birthday hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag!
Hashtag FWMCBDay26, that is!
Please post your thoughts, pictures, and screenshots with hashtag FWMCBDay26!
We'll check out all your thoughts after the show!
Also, we're going to be having
a special membership-only concert right after this!
So don't miss it, okay?
Yay!
最後にはメインゲンのアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
At the very end, there's also an encore live, so please come watch!
You know, it is a concert after all!
So we get singing a little bit more, yeah? Yeah!
So we get to sing a little bit more, yeah? Yeah!
For this next song, I think we need a special guest for this, right?
Yeah! Let's call her out together!
Calliope!
Hey everyone!
Today only, I am also a dog.
FuwaMoco dog!
Thank you for coming to my birthday!
Thank you for inviting me, I'm happy to be here. What's up, Ruffians?
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh? I do!
Wow, look at this logo! What could it say? Check it out.
With respect, with respect, with respect!
You know, and it would be cute if we matched right?
But maybe we'll just go run and we'll continue with the dog faces or something?
Okay, you could do it. I got this. They won't bite. They won't bite.
Okay!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's Super Special Splits Challenge segment!
Ikuzo!
Let's go!
Thinking I can! Thinking I can't! I'm sorry, I can't! I can't do it!
I did my best!
We seemed to be the same, right? But I can't do it soon there.
That's right! We're matching! Tripling! Tripling!
That's a nice ring to it. And this next song is with FuwaMoco.
We wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Something nostalgic, and I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap in there as well.
But it's also very cute, right?
次歌う曲はキャリさんパパと一緒でずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です。
The next song we're singing is one we've always wanted to sing with Calli-papa, a song we love so much.
It's both cute! It's cool!
But I think you know it shares an important part that, no, you should be proud of what you like, right?
And more in meaning of being proud, being strong about what you like, yeah, your likes, and maybe that be games or anime or idol, figure, or maybe even VTubers!
After all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right? Definitely! And so we're going to sing this song for you guys!
Let's do the title call together, okay? Listen to this!
Like! Like! Like!
Comic, I like it!
Music, I like it!
Game, I like it!
Animation, I like it!
Figure, I like it!
Movie, I like it!
Wonder, I like it!
Hobby, I like it!
Go go go go go go go go go!
Do you like it? I like it!
You like it? I like it!
神社仏閣信仰のモノガタリサウナ
Shinto shrines, temples, beliefs, a story of sauna
好きなもの好きでいたならそれはスーパーノヴァ
If you stay true to what you love, that's a supernova!
開口一番接触マックスの笑い声
Right off the bat, maximum contact laughter
丸で出来た鍵穴ルシカって言う檀家ドメイン
A danka domain called "Lucifer" with a keyhole made of circles
プラスチック マジック モウリ クドクデクメン 切っても軸は一緒でしょ？
Plastic magic Mori Kudoku Dekumen, even if you cut it, the core is the same, right?
飲み水きらめきのソラ 今すぐレッツミックスダウン！
Drinking water, glittering sky, let's mix down right now!
罪が平穏にだって民屑ればこんさーん
Even if sin is peaceful, if the masses gather, it's chaotic!
一体どうなりどうなりどうなり ジャッカル野暮せよフュー！
What on earth is going on, jackal-like unrefined nonsense, whew!
I Like It! I Like It! スキになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you come to love it,
きっと全てがカラフルで
Surely everything will be colorful,
Lucky! Lucky! 惜しくさえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even with regret,
光る宝物さ
It's a shining treasure!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I finally got to meet you,
やっと「今日からヨロシクね」
And finally say, "Nice to meet you starting today."
ホラ、キラキラ夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, it's like a glittering dream, I want to embrace you quickly
アレもコレも欲しくて 神様に祈ってる
Wanting both this and that, praying to the gods
ふわふわ もこもこ
Fuwawa, Mococo!
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Underworld Guard Dog Sisters ☆★
この世界に爆誕“BAU”dolです
Exploding into this world as “BAU”dols!
BAUBAU!!
BAU BAU!!
Always the same, walking around, you know what I'm talking about, yeah, word like, like cat
360度パノラマ全方大好きのZEN
360-degree panorama, full direction, loving ZEN!
何が起きたっていいからのみこめる自分のアイテムライクアスーパースターファイアメン
Whatever happens is fine, my own item that I can swallow like a superstar fireman!
無敵アンディ他方大体ライセ望んでる彼もきっと
Invincible Andy, elsewhere mostly the next world, whoever desires it surely...
現世が愛おしくなるはずなのさ
will find this mortal world endearing!
奈落を通すとなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんで歩こうぜNight
It's not about passing through the abyss, let's enjoy life and walk through the night!
自分に素直であれ Spot light 僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, spotlight, shine upon us!
今日も愛は叫ぶだけだ Get down!
Today too, love is just shouting out, get down!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hands,
きっと全てがミラクルで
surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you,
ずっと離さないでいてね
never let me go!
ほら キラキラ滲みみたい 世界は回りだす
Look, like a shimmering rainbow, the world begins to spin!
HEY!! RUFFIANS!! KEPT YOU WAITING, HUH?
CAN I GET A HECK YEAH!?
LET’S SHOUT “BAU”!!
BAU!! BAU!! BAU!! BAU!!
NOW, HEAR THE HOWLING OF MY SOUL!! ARE YOU READY!?
BAU BAU!!
好き好き好き好きショウブ大カーテンに
Like, like, like, like, opening the big curtain of the show,
入れたいこの感情 どめとさいて本気検証
I want to put this emotion in, stop it and prove it seriously!
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう 恋ももっと事件
That's right, love is even more of an incident,
でもそれが僕のド真剣
but that's my total seriousness!
素直になれたなら Happy Days
If we can be honest, happy days!
I Like It! I Like It! スキになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you come to love it,
きっと全てがカラフルで
surely everything will be colorful!
Lucky! Lucky! 星くずさえ 光る宝物さ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust is a shining treasure!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた やっと今日からよろしくね
I Like It! I Like It! I finally met you, let's get along from today!
ほら キラキラ 夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, like a shimmering dream, I want to embrace you quickly!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out your hands,
きっと全てがミラクルで
surely everything will be a miracle!
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life is a dream story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた ずっと離さないでいてね
I Like It! I Like It! I met you, never let me go!
ほら キラキラ 滲みみたい 世界は回りだす
Look, like a shimmering rainbow, the world begins to spin!
I like FUWAMOCO!
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ！
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
街角に並ぶ映画のポスター もうこの街にも飽きたわ
Movie posters on the street corner, I'm already sick of this town.
受話器の向こうに溜息をつく 「キャンセルしないで…」
Sighing on the other side of the receiver, "Don't cancel on me..."
ハートのロケットに隠した写真 誰も知らないホンキの恋 神様は気づいてる
A photo hidden in a heart locket, a true love nobody knows, God knows.
je t’aime ★ je t’aime 叶えない夢なんて見たくないわ でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
je t’aime ★ je t’aime, I don't want unfulfilled dreams, but romance is awakening.
“ 愛してるわ ” クレープに描く愛の傘の下で 止まぬ雨の音
"I love you", under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe, the sound of unending rain.
je t’aime ★ je t’aime 叶えない夢なんて見たくないわ でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
je t’aime ★ je t’aime, I don't want unfulfilled dreams, but romance is awakening.
“ 愛してるわ ” クレープに描く愛の傘の下で 止まぬ雨の音
"I love you", under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe, the sound of unending rain.
je t’aime ★ je t’aime
こんなお台場の夜に
On a night like this in Odaiba,
したくはないから
I don't want to spend it alone...
ほんの五分でも…逢いたい
Even just for five minutes... I want to see you.
止みそうもない
The rain shows no sign of stopping,
猫をどうしようも
and I don't know what to do with the cats either...
あなたがいないと
Without you here,
つまらない だけどポケットに
life is so dull! But in my pocket,
入れたままのコインに
with the coin I left right there,
賭けるわ
I'll take a chance.
恋の行方 神様が知っている
God knows where this love is heading.
Je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring love affair at all!
あっ、と言う間に溺れてく
Before I know it, I'm drowning in it.
“今がすべて”カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
"The present is everything"—before the café au lait gets cold,
もういちどKISSして
kiss me once more.
Je t'aime ★ je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Locking away the story,
De jour en jour あなたのことばかりを夢見ている
De jour en jour... I'm only dreaming of you.
もぉなにも…
No more...
Je t'aime ★ je t'aime
叶えない夢なんて見たくないわ
I don't want to see unfulfilled dreams!
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
Yet romance awakens within me.
“愛してるわ”クレープに描く愛の傘の下で
"I love you"—under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe,
止まぬ雨の音
the sound of endless rain falls.
Je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring love affair at all!
あっ、と言う間に溺れてく
Before I know it, I'm drowning in it.
“今がすべて”カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
"The present is everything"—before the café au lait gets cold,
もういちど聞かせて
let me hear it once more.
Je t'aime ★ je t'aime
ラララ…
La la la...
Wow! We can't stay already! Perfect timing!
Well, that love song was... Je t'aime, je t'aime! What do you think, Ruffians?
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic as well, you know, with some city pop vibes too!
And the choreography is cute too, right?
Well, we hope it made you feel nice, our warm and fluffy Ruffians!
You know, with the sun setting now, it's starting to feel a bit... romantic, almost, right?
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call up our next guest!
AZKi-senpai! Aki Rosenthal-senpai!
Happy birthday!!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！自己紹介お願いします！
Thank you so much! Please introduce yourselves!
ど、ど、ど、AZKi、AZKiです！
I-I-I'm AZKi! AZKi here!
はい、ホルカ星の妖精、アキ・ローゼンタールことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
Yes, I'm Holka Star fairy, Aki Rosenthal, aka Aki Rosenthal!
おめでとー！おめでとー！すてきすてき！
Happy birthday! Congratulations! So wonderful!
誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
えー、すごい！おめでとうございます！
Wow, amazing! Congratulations!
ね、あの、AZKi先輩とアキ・ローゼンタール先輩の歌声がすごく大好きなので…
You know, we love AZKi-senpai and Aki Rosenthal-senpai's singing voices so much...
一緒に出演することができて、本当…
and getting to sing together with you really...
アキローゼ先輩とあずき先輩は
Akirose-senpai and Azuki-senpai
とっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので、
are such charming older sisters, so...
あら、そうなんですか？
Oh, is that so?
えっと、この曲で行こうかなと思いました。
Um, I thought we could go with this song.
あらあら！
Oh my!
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし。
Well, it's getting a bit dark too.
確かに、ちょっと夕方だ。ちょっとドラマチックになりましたね。
That's true, it's a bit like evening. It's gotten a bit dramatic, hasn't it?
実はちょっぴりセクシーかも！
Actually, it might be a bit sexy!
セクシーかも？セクシーな曲？
Sexy? A sexy song?
じゃあ、したことある？
So, have you ever done it?
私はしたことあたいですけど。
I'd love to do it though.
なににに？
What, what, what?
アキローゼ先輩、えっと、この曲を歌う前に少し、あの、セクシーなうーまっぷ...
Akirose-senpai, um, before singing this song, a little, you know, sexy warm-up...
おお、してもいいですか？いいですか？
Oh, can we do it? Is it okay?
セクシーウォームアップ、オッケー！
Sexy warm-up, ok!
じゃあ、まずセクシーな体を作るために
Well, first, to make a sexy body...
自分のボディをなでて！
caress your own body!
なでて？
Caress?
なでてなでて！あ、たまに！
Caress, caress! Oh, occasionally!
足から、足からぶつから...
From your legs, from your legs, bump...
なでて！なでて！なでて！
Caress! Caress! Caress!
だってだって見て！だって！
But, but look! But!
はずかしがらずに！
Without being shy!
なでてね、アキローゼ先輩みたいに！
Caress, like Akirose-senpai!
あ、モモちゃんちょっと、はい、いいよ！オッケー！いいよ！
Ah, Moco-chan, a bit, yes, that's good! Okay! That's good!
じゃあもう一回ウォームアップしていきましょうか！いいですか？
Well, shall we do the warm-up once more? Is it good?
じゃあまずセクシーだ、体を作るために！セクシーウォームアップ！
Well, first, to make a sexy body! Sexy warm-up!
もうちょっと、もう一回！もうちょっと違うかな？
Once more, one more time! Is it a bit different?
あずきちゃんの中ではセクシーだけど可愛い、ちょっと違うのかな？
In Azuki-chan's mind, it's sexy yet cute, maybe a bit different?
やっぱこうやって、お、こう？
As expected, like this, oh, like this?
おお、セクシー！尻とか！あ、尻！あ、尻！
Oh, sexy! Butt and such! Ah, butt! Ah, butt!
尻！あ、しっぽふりふり！しっぽふりふり！モコちゃんしっぽ！しっぽふりふり！
Butt! Ah, tail wagging! Tail wagging! Moco-chan's tail! Tail wagging!
ウォームアップ、ウォームアップ、ぷりぷりぷりぷり、ぷりぷりぷりぷり！オッケーオッケー！
Warm-up, warm-up, puripuri, puripuri, okay okay!
いいじゃない！いいじゃない！いいよいいよ！もっとできてた！もっとできてた！
Not bad! Not bad! That's good! You could do more! You could do more!
じゃあ、1時になりましたね！
Well, it's 1 o'clock now!
はい、次の曲行きましょうか！
Yes, shall we go to the next song?
じゃあ、聞いてください、ディスコテック！
Well then, please listen, DISCOTHEQUE!
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(DISCO LADY DISCO LADY DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN' Let's dance,
はじける BEAUTY LADY
the bursting BEAUTY LADY!
生まれ変わって甘い夢
I want to be reborn and softly color
そっと彩りたいの
the sweet dream...
グラマラスなくちびる
The glamorous lips and
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
the pink nails shining with gloss,
ガラスの向こう側に映る素顔
the true face reflected on the other side of the glass,
シュールなDays
the surreal days.
キミだけにSO 見せていたい
I want to show the inside of my heart,
心の中 瞳の奥
deep within my eyes only to you.
AH 傍にいて欲しいよ
AH I want you to be near
月のMIRROR BALL 照らされて
as the moon's mirror ball shines on us.
MY DARLIN' ねえ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょ
MY DARLIN' Hey let's fall in a vivid love,
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
bursting SEXY BEAUTY!
生まれ変わって甘い夢
My love is reborn and softly color
そっと彩る MY LOVE ほら 世界は変わる
the sweet dream, see, the world can change.
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
ドラマティックな情熱 褪せないデジャヴ
Wanting to continue watching the dramatic passion,
見つめたくて
the fadeless deja vu...
カラフルなSWEETY STORY 心深く
The colorful SWEETY STORY is engraved
刻み込む
deeply in my heart.
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if the small darkness visits,
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
if the spell of love is chanted,
そう、きっと 果てない空 星屑のSHOWERが降り注ぐ
yes, the shower of stardust will rain in the endless sky.
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
That's why I aim for the HAPPY STATION
50/50あわせて
by matching the 50/50,
100%以上の愛
I'm thinking that love more than 100%
揺るぎなくここにあると私思ってる
is firmly here.
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
キスしてもいいですか？なんて聞いてこないでよもう！
Can I kiss you? Don't ask me that already!
ホーリーナイトくらい前のめり心溶かしてよ
Holly Night, melt my heart before we go further!
ディナーしてお酒飲んでそこまではいのを
We had dinner and drinks, why stop right there?
期待して待ってるのにそのあと続かない
I'm expecting so much, don't leave me hanging!
腕くらい組んできてほしいのになんでよもう！
Can't you at least link arms with me already!
ホーリーナイトでもオクテすぎる頼ないマイダーリン
Holly Night, you're way too shy, my darlin'!
付き合って一ヶ月よ友達じゃないの
We've been dating for a month, we're not just friends!
ねえ彼女にそんなこと言わせないでよもう！
Hey, don't say things like that to your girlfriend!
キスしてもいいですか？なんて聞いてこないでよもう！
Can I kiss you? Don't ask me that already!
ホーリーナイトくらい前のめり心溶かしてよ
Holly Night, melt my heart before we go further!
イルミネーションと冬の匂いが拍車かける
The illumination and the scent of winter set the mood.
ホーリーナイトだろほら引っ張ってでお姫様させて
Holly Night, come on, pull me close and treat me like a princess!
腕くらい組んできてほしいのになんでよもう！
Can't you at least link arms with me already!
ホーリーナイトでもオクテすぎる頼ないマイダーリン
Holly Night, you're way too shy, my darlin'!
それでも私を選んでくれた素敵な人
Even so, you're the wonderful person I chose,
頼ないけど誰よりもそう大好きよマイダーリン
You may be unreliable, but I love you more than anyone, my darlin'!
MY DARLIN' ねぇヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My Darlin'! Let's feel this vivid love!
はじけるSEXY BEAUTY
It's sparkling, sexy and beauty!
生まれ変わって甘い夢そっと包むMY LOVEほら
A sweet dream born anew, gently cradling My Love, behold!
世界は変わる
The world is changing!
チュルチュルチュルパヤパパ
Chu-lu-chu-lu-chu-lu-pa-pa-pa!
燃え尽きるわこの恋たぶん
This love is going to burn right out.
どんな終幕が来ようとも覚悟してるわ
No matter what kind of ending comes, I am prepared.
余裕なんてほとんどない
I hardly have any breathing room,
必死にしがみついているだけ
I'm just desperately holding on.
貴方の目優しく抱き寄せる腕
Your eyes, and the arms that gently pull me in...
すべてがすべてが初めてのfall in loveだったわ
Everything, everything was my first fall in love.
kiss me離さないで
Kiss me, don't let go.
kiss me自然なままで
Kiss me, keep it natural.
この不安を拭いとってねぇ…
Wipe away this insecurity, hey...
touch meその指先
Touch me with those fingertips.
touch meその眼差しで
Touch me with that gaze.
この私を包み込んでplease…
Wrap me up entirely, please...
愛してる
I love you.
よみがえるわ昨日のこと
Yesterday's moments come back to life,
あんなに心が揺れたの
My heart was shaken so much.
初めてだもの
It's a first for me,
寂しすぎて時に怖い
It's so lonely, sometimes it's scary.
二人で居れないこの時が
This time when we can't be together—
雨の朝暖かい部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room.
大人のふりから
Playing at being adults,
本当の大人になれそう
I feel like I'm becoming a true adult.
kiss me危険なほど
Kiss me, so dangerous.
kiss me甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss.
この願いを全部叶えてねぇ…
Make all of these wishes come true, hey...
knock meその魂で
Knock me with your soul.
knock me窓を叩いて
Knock me, hit the window.
この私を安心させてplease…
Put my mind at ease, please...
愛してる
I love you.
kiss me危険なほど
Kiss me, so dangerous.
kiss me甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss.
この願いを全部叶えてねぇ…
Make all of these wishes come true, hey...
knock meその魂で
Knock me with your soul.
knock me窓を叩いて
Knock me, hit the window.
この私を安心させてplease…
Put my mind at ease, please...
愛してる
I love you.
kiss me危険なほど
Kiss me, so dangerous.
kiss me甘い口づけ
Kiss me, a sweet kiss.
この願いを全部叶えてねぇ…
Make all of these wishes come true, hey...
knock meその魂で
Knock me with your soul.
knock me窓を叩いて
Knock me, hit the window.
この私を安心させてplease…
Put my mind at ease, please...
愛してる
I love you.
Kiss me 言い慣れないほど
Kiss me, more than I'm used to saying
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, with a sweet kiss
こんな願いを全部叶えてね
Grant all of these wishes of mine, okay?
ねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇねぇ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
Knock me その魂で
Knock me, with that soul of yours
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on my window
こんな私を安心させて please
Put me at ease like this, please
Please please please please please please
Please, please, please, please...
愛してる
I love you
Day by day 日に日に
Day by day, day by day
慕うの 乙女心
My maiden heart yearns for you
おんなじクラス 斜め前のおとなしい人
The quiet boy sitting diagonally in front in the same class
カッコ良くはない だけど優しい
He's not cool, but he's kind
いつも頼れる彼
Always someone I can rely on
After school 恋愛相談の帰り道
After school, on the walk home from talking about love
なんだって話せる親友の女の子
My best girl friend whom I can talk to about anything
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて
Good at sports, good at studying too
女子力MAXです
And her femininity is at max!
どこにでもある よくあること
It happens everywhere, it happens all the time
急に彼女が
Suddenly she says,
「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの…！」って
"Um, actually, there's someone I like..."!
ちょ、マジで！？
Who, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
Like a cliché manga flag
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて残念すぎます！
Never thought I'd be the one to set it up myself, it's such a shame!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable
なんちゃってなんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding, just kidding" won't cut it in this category
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship flicker back and forth
なんか青春しちゃいます
It feels a bit like youth
わたし困っちゃいます
I'm in quite a bind!
完璧です お似合いすぎます勝てっこない
So perfect, you suit each other so well, I can't win
くやしいけどとかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's not that I'm frustrated, this is from the bottom of my heart
てゆーかすでに応援モード
I'm already in full support mode
むしろ清々しい
I actually feel quite refreshed
だけど彼女は 不思議な顔
But she has a mysterious look on her face
真剣な目で
With serious eyes
「そうじゃなくて、私あなたが好き…ゴメン」って
"It's not that, it's you that I love... sorry"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
わたし あなた 彼女とわたし
Me, you, she and me
超絶！複雑！百合展開は想定外です！
Extremely! Complicated! A yuri development is unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable
なんちゃってなんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding, just kidding" won't cut it in this category
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
You gave me an unsolvable puzzle
神よ恨んじゃいます わたし悩んじゃいます
Oh God, I resent you, I'm so worried
「あっ！もう！スゴイヤバイ！」
"Ah, jeez! This is super crazy!"
「好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくてっ！」
"I like you? I like you, but... wait, not in that way!"
「だって…女の子同士だし…」
"Because... we're both girls after all..."
「ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？」
"Hey God, what should I do?"
「わたし、どうしたらいいの？」
"What should I do?"
「ヘルプメーーーッ！！！」
"Help meeeeee!!!"
なんか変だー 愛に国境も枷も性別もない！
Something's weird—love knows no borders, shackles, or gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
普通の恋夢見てたのに
Even though I was dreaming of a normal love
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃ ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
For a normal-setting me, this game is way too impossible!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable
なんちゃってなんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding, just kidding" won't cut it in this category
彼女のこと好きになれたらなんて妄想しちゃいます…
I catch myself fantasizing about what if I could fall in love with her...
わたしどうしかしています
I must be losing my mind
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is so fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
In an instant, in an instant, the balance crumbles
わたし あなた 彼女とわたし
Me, you, she and me
超絶！複雑！百合展開は想定外です！
Extremely! Complicated! A yuri development is unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable
なんちゃってなんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding, just kidding" won't cut it in this category
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
You gave me an unsolvable puzzle
神よ恨んじゃいます わたし悩んじゃいます
Oh God, I resent you, I'm so worried
私 悩んじゃいます
I'm worrying about it...
すごい やばい
Super crazy!
ていうかよ すっぴんだけど ていう意味じゃなくて だって 女の子同士だし
I mean, not like that! We're both girls, you know!
ねぇ神様 どうしたらいいの？ 私 どうしたいの？
Hey God, what should I do? What do I want?
ヘルプミー！
Help me!
なんか変だ アイに国境もセックスも関係ない
Love knows no borders or gender!
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangular love is fickle,
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
and in an instant, the balance falls apart.
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
I was dreaming of a normal love,
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
but for a normal setting, this is way too hardcore!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangular love is unstable,
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
a category where "just kidding" doesn't cut it.
彼女のこと 好きになれたなら
If I could come to love her,
なんて妄想しちゃいます
what a wild daydream that would be...
わたし どうかしてます
I must be going crazy.
Oh, wow! Thank you so much, Fuwawa! That was so much fun!
Yeah, it was! I got a bit dizzy though, with the bubbles and changing so quickly!
Yeah, it was so fast!
You know, the bubble dance is a little bit silly, but it was so surprising!
And we got to see you as well, even more close up than usual! Yeah!
Well, those last two songs were Kiss Me, I Stated It Together with Alvins, and Triangle Dreamer!
Yeah, with Wicky's Senpai, Mew's Senpai, and Suisei's Senpai!
What do you think of this? Kiss Me, I Stated It..., it's a song that I've always wanted to sing together with Alvins!
Yeah, it's a little bit more sexy song, no? A sexy song, huh?
Yeah, and Triangle Dreamer, the festival idol song!
Yeah! So Yily Tenkai was too quick, and Laffians are you still alive?
Wow, wow! My Oshi Senpai were so cute in love!
Yeah! And Man Crates, we got the bubbles! It was a blast!
A lot of bliss this year, right? Yeah!
Well, we have a tiny announcement! You know, it's our birthday, right?
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you! Okay, yeah!
Birthday Set 2026!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with our FuwaMoco 2026 Birthday Merch!
フワモコの生誕グッズ紹介、始まりやーす！
Let's start introducing Fuwamoco's birthday merch!
Fuwa Fuwa Idol☆Fuwawa Acrylic Stand. You can display them side by side!
イラスト：イクセモチ。約H30cm。
Illustration by Ikumochi. Approx. H30cm.
Ehehe Angel☆Rubber Figurine, and HOEH?! Devil☆Rubber Figurine.
えへへえんじぇる☆ラバーマスコット、HOEH?!てびる☆ラバーマスコット
Palm-sized figures perfect for displaying on your desk.
Yappy Puppy☆FuwaWawa Sounds Plushie and Yappy Puppy☆Mococo Sounds Plushie.
おしゃべりぱぴー☆FUWAWAVAぬいぐるみ
Contains 22 original voice packs!
おしゃべりぱぴー☆MOCOCOぬいぐるみのふわモコだよ！
It's the Oshaberi Puppy ☆ MOCOCO Plushie Fuwamoco!
ぎゅっとすると、いろいろしゃべるよ。
Give it a hug, and it'll say all sorts of things!
どんなボイスが出るか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to hearing what kind of voice it has!
Fuwawa to GO☆Finger Puppet
Fuwawa to GO☆ Finger Puppet!
And they both come with one extra Ruffian's figurine costume you can dress up in and bring around with you everywhere!
FUWAVAの指パペットと、
FUWAVA's finger puppet,
どこでも一緒に連れていけるサイズで着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
in a size you can take anywhere, complete with a dress-up Ruffians costume!
ASMR Voice Pack "Back from a Fluffy Date" & "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy"
Featuring two ASMR voice packs: "Back from a Fluffy Date" and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy"!
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
珍しい初ピッツソファイス！ Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
The merch is separated into two sets: Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch.
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはふわふわセットとモコモコセットに分かれています。
The goods are separated into the Fuwawa set and Mococo set.
セットごとにチェキ風カードと特典ボイスが付きます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card and bonus voice!
The full set version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは直筆サイン付きだよ！
The limited edition sets come with handwritten signatures!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさんの愛を込めてサイン書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into writing our signatures!
Please check out the Hololive official online shop and look for the link in the description!
ぜひ、ホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！
Be sure to check the official Hololive shop!
What do you think, Ruffians? Our birthday merch is pretty cute, huh?
Well, the reservations will be going on sale right after the birthday live here ends!
そう！サタンのグッズの予約枠はこのあと開始しますので、お忘れずにチェックしてくださいね！
That's right! Reservations for the birthday merch start right after this, so don't forget to check it out!
Don't forget, okay? We put a lot of love into it... Time to go, go, go!
We performed more special collab solos with our dear senpais!
まだ会ったことない、謎のゲストが1人いるんだよね！
But there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
Well, should we give the Ruffians a hint more?
Ruffians are curious, right?
ほっぺたピー？ Yagoo-san?
Cheeky P? Yagoo-san?
ふたつぐかす？ Maybe... What could it be?
Maybe... What could it be?
Maybe you should get ready, because you know, they aren't quite as bad as Peroro...
もこちゃん、you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Mococo, you're not going to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Well, we'll see! Wow, let's get them out here then! Who could it be, who could it be?
せーの！どうぞー！
Ready, set! Here they go!
わーわーわーわー！きたしんよ！きたしんよ！キュンキュン！
Wah wah wah wah! He's here, dashin yo! Kyun kyun!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！わーわーわー！
I'm Kuro-chan! Wah wah wah!
きたしんよ！はじめまして！
He's here, dashin yo! Nice to meet you!
ちわわじゃないよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua!
フワワじゃないよ、フワモコだよ！モコモコじゃないよ、モコモコだよ！
Not Fuwawa, we're Fuwamoco! Not Mococo, it's Mococo!
二人合わせて、フワモコです！こんばんはー！
Together, we are Fuwamoco! Good evening!
こんばんは！よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いします！
Good evening! Nice to meet you!
フワモコのわちゃわちゃバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Fuwamoco's chaotic birthday festival!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ！フワモコ！イェーイ！しんしん！
Happy birthday, dashin yo! Fuwamoco! Yay! Shin shin!
えーっと、視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど、クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
Um, I think there are many viewers who are Ruffians, could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
え、自分ですんのそれを？そう！
Eh, you want me to do it myself? That's right!
自己紹介！わかったしんよ。だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね！海外のチームも分かる自己紹介しますからね！
Self-introduction! I understand, dashin yo. After all, people overseas are watching too! I'll do a self-introduction that overseas fans will understand!
ナイスミートぅ！ナイスミートぅ！チューチューチューチューチューリップ！
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Chuu chuu chuu chuu tulip!
は？あお？やだ！え、ちょっと困らないで！え、クロちゃんは？チューリップ？いやチューリップじゃない、ちょっとまだ分からないかもしれないから...
Ha? Ao? No way! Hey, don't be troubled! Hey, Kuro-chan is? Tulip? No, not a tulip, maybe you don't know yet so...
ええとね、安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでるえっと、芸人さんで、あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってまして、作詞とかもしてます！クロちゃんです！
Um, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus, and I'm also the producer of Mameshiba no Taigun, and I write lyrics too! I'm Kuro-chan!
わーわー！じゃあ今回は英語でお願いします！イングリッシュ！
Wah wah! Then this time, please do it in English! English!
僕が？Yes! 自分 で？Yes!
Me? Yes! By myself? Yes!
え、そんなこと急に言われたらイッツ シャイニング フラワー！
Eh, if you suddenly tell me that... It's shining flower!
言い訳はないし
There's no excuse.
聞いてる人の話
That's what the listeners are saying.
ねえ、頑張って！
Hey, do your best!
えっと、なんだろ、なんだろ、えっと…
Umm, I wonder, I wonder, umm...
フェイフェイマス・コメディアン
Famous comedian,
アイドルプロデューサー！
an idol producer!
やってるしんよ！
I'm doing that, shin!
お、できる！です！うんうん
Oh, you can! Yes! Yeah, yeah.
クロちゃん、テレビでよく見てるけど…
Kuro-chan, we see you on TV all the time, but...
ちょっと、ふわモコのペットのペロちゃんと、えっとちょっと似てるところが、たくさんあるね！
you're a lot like Fuwamoco's pet, Pero-chan!
えっ、ちょっと後ろの、数を見てください！
Hey, look at the number in the back!
そうするとペロです！
That makes it Pero!
ちょっと待て、球体っていうか丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait a minute, isn't it just the sphere-like, round part?
だけじゃない！
Not just that!
えっと、クロちゃんと似てるところは…
Umm, the parts that look like Kuro-chan are...
嘘好きで、女の子好きで…
He loves lying, loves girls...
よろしく！
Nice to meet you!
だからね、認めで騙されないで！え、クロちゃんはそんなに大丈夫なの？って言われて…
So don't be fooled! "Kuro-chan, are you really okay with that?" people ask...
いや、ひどい！悲しくなってきた！
No, that's awful! I'm getting sad!
え、え、え、え、本当に！
Seriously, seriously!
遠目で応援、ふっ！
Cheering from afar, hmph!
全然人の話聞いてないよね、君たちは！
You guys aren't listening to people at all!
できるばあ…
Can we...
クロちゃんは、ペロの友達になってくれませんか？
Kuro-chan, won't you become Pero's friend?
え、ふわモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達なの？
Huh? Not Fuwamoco's friend, but Pero's friend?
いや、ふわモコはクロちゃんのお友達になりたくないから！
Yeah, because Fuwamoco doesn't want to be Kuro-chan's friend!
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that strange?
いや、いや、いや、気持ち悪いから！
No, no, no, because it's creepy!
気持ち悪くない！マニアには受ける！
It's not creepy! Maniacs love it!
いや、違う！ふわも気持ち悪い、やっぱり！
No, way! Fuwa thinks it's creepy after all!
でもでもモコちゃん、ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼です！
But Moco-chan, that's going too far, it's rude!
いや、もし、もしもペロと仲良くなりたいんだったら、ふわモコちゃんクロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだほうがいいんじゃない？
Well, if you want to get along with Pero, shouldn't Fuwamoco-chan ask Kuro-chan nicely?
はあ？え、の？え、の？
Huh? Eh, no? Eh, no?
しっかりとしたして！
Get a grip!
え、ま、けどペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ！
Well, but Pero is cute, so I think it's fine to become friends!
うれしい！うれしい！可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたらうれしいかな！
Yay! Yay! Not cute, but I'd be happy if we became friends!
感情が、感情が色々ありすぎなのよ、本当に！
You have too many emotions going on, really!
まあまあ、クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？
Well, Kuro-chan is a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
ね！
Right?
そう、もともとアイドルになろうと思ったのに騙されて芸人にさせられたから…
Yeah, originally I wanted to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian...
アイドルは本当に夢、ドリーム！
Idols are truly a dream!
なんか悲しいね、かわいそう！
That's kind of sad, poor thing!
でもドリームって大事でしょ？
But a dream is important, right?
大事！
Important!
そ、で、ま、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから、もうせっかく一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
So, since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol, won't you sing together with us?
えー、いいしや、いいしや！
Eh, okay, okay!
ノリノリでやれる曲ね？この曲ってどうの曲ね？
A song we can get hyped to? What kind of song is this?
あの、ハードル上げないで！
Hey, don't raise the bar!
大丈夫！そう、ね？アイドルのプロデュースもやってるし、実力見せてよ！
It's fine! Right? You produce idols too, so show us your skills!
オッケーだしんよ、行くしんよ、行くしんよ！
Okay, shin! Let's go, shin!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a super cute song together!
なんの曲？
What song?
楽しみ！
Looking forward to it!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！
Now, let's do the title call together!
せーの、ちゅ、多様性！
Ready, go: Chu, Tayousei!
多様性なの？
Tayousei?
我愛你 酔いが覚めない
I love you, I haven't sobered up yet
oh, i need you 恋が覚めない
Oh, I need you, still drunk on love
お生憎様の慣れ果て果てして
You get what you deserve in the end
無問題 破滅してみて
No problem, try and ruin yourself
hold me tight トラウマの味も
Hold me tight, even the taste of trauma
猛反対 お手 お座りでハイ♡報酬
Total opposition, paw, sit for a high reward♡
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is tingling
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is pounding
鼓動で孤独消してみてよ
Drown out loneliness with your heartbeat
愛も恋も独裁して 僕を独占して
Dictate love and romance, monopolize me
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよ
Let's kiss until we become addicted
get get get on! get get get on! get on chu!
熱く とろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
Overflowing with emotion, melting hot
たまらないでしょ
Irresistible, isn't it?
get get get on! get get get on! get on chu!
我愛你 無問題 get get get on chu!
I love you, no problem, get get get on chu!
get get get on! get get get on! get on chu!
ポンチカン 勝負はいつも
Pon-chi-kan, a game is always
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Ton-chin-kan, according to me
チンプンカンプンだ 最後はロンでしょ?
It's all Greek to me, isn't it ron at the end?
もう何回? やられればいい
How many more times should I get killed?
oh, one night 忘れられない
Oh, One night, I can never forget
終わんないで トキメキ 伝愛♡予習
Don't end yet, our heart-pounding love preparation ♡
喉の奥がチクンチクン
My throat is tingling...
僕はドキンドキン
My heart is pounding...
心臓ごと 引きずり出してみせてよ
Drag out my heart and show it to me!
きもちいいね 面倒くさいけど やっぱ照れくさいけど
It feels so good, even if it's troublesome and embarrassing.
死ぬまで 忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget until we die.
いかれた街は ゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies.
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me.
ドキメキ胸につながる ロープを引きなよ
Pull the rope connected to your pounding heart!
Bet on chu! Bet on chu! Bet on chu! Bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの美しさが 美しいでしょ
A beauty so intense it makes you go crazy is beautiful, right?
Get on chu! Get on chu! Get on chu! Get on chu!
せーの ポン・チ・カン 終わんない Get Get Get on chu!
Ready, set... Pon-Chi-Kan, it never ends, Get Get Get on chu!
我爱你 無問題 Get Get Get on chu!
Wǒ ài nǐ, wú wèntí, Get Get Get on chu!
わー！やったー！うまくいったしよー！
Yay! We did it! It went so well!
ありがとう！よかったー！
Thank you! I'm so glad!
頑張ったね、クロちゃん！楽しかった！ありがとう！
You did your best, Kuro-chan! We had fun, thank you!
えー、ちょっとね、さよならする前に、えっと、1個お願いしてもいいですか？
Um, before we say goodbye, can I ask one favor?
1個だけだしいよ！1個だけじゃん？
Only one! Just one?
えっと、フワモコは魔界の冒険でがおーをよく言ってるんですけど、
Umm, FuwaMoco often says 'gao' in our Makai adventures,
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、フワモコのように可愛いがおーをしてもらえますか？
so Kuro-chan, can you look at the camera and do a cute 'gao' like FuwaMoco?
えー！できるかな！？いくしよー！がおーがおー！
Eh?! Can I do it?! Here we go! Gao! Gao!
えっ！それがベスト！？
Eh?! Was that your best?!
もう1回！もっとやって！
One more time! Do it more!
がおーがおー！かわいいかな？
Gao! Gao! Was that cute?
実はもう1個やりたいことがあるんですけど。
Actually, there's one more thing we want to do.
なに？ さっきほどやりましたけど、フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって、
What? We did it earlier, but FuwaMoco has our usual self-introduction,
できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
and we'd love to do it together with all three of us!
おー！あれ可愛かったからやりたいクロちゃんも！
Oh! That was cute, Kuro-chan wants to do it too!
じゃあ行きますよ！
Then let's go!
フワワじゃないよ、フワモコだよ！
It's not Fuwawa, it's FuwaMoco!
ワーワーワーワーワー！ フワモコじゃないよ、クロちゃんだよ！クロちゃんじゃないよ、ボクボクだよ！
Wawawawa! It's not FuwaMoco, it's Kuro-chan! It's not Kuro-chan, it's Boku-boku!
段々に合わせて！なんで、怒んないで、どうしたの？
Match the rhythm! Why are you getting mad, what's wrong?
だって、クロちゃん！言ってかないから、何なんそれ？
Because, Kuro-chan! You're not saying it right, what is that?
おい！もう嘘とかつくんなよ！おい！
Hey! Stop telling lies already! Hey!
モコちゃん、パイイチしちゃおう！
Mococo, let's give him a pie kick!
なんでプンプン怒んないで、どうしたの？
Why are you so angry, what's wrong?
落ち着いて、落ち着いて！なんで？
Calm down, calm down! Why?
大丈夫、モコちゃん大丈夫！
It's okay, Mococo is okay!
じゃ、クロちゃんはこれからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
マジで！？ あ、本当？
Seriously?! Ah, really?
じゃあ、モコちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね！
Then Mococo, let's high-five Kuro-chan and say goodbye!
仲直り、仲直り、いい？ ハイタッチ、ハイタッチ！
Make up, make up, okay? High five, high five!
ほらほらほら！やってみて！仲直り、仲直り！なんで怒っちゃったの？
Come on, come on! Try it! Make up, make up! Why did you get mad?
ひどくないもう、ちょっと！何なの？けど
Isn't that awful, hey! What's with that?
フワモコちゃん、本当に お誕生日おめでとうございます！
FuwaMoco-chan, truly happy birthday!
きゅんからのバキュン、おめでとうハート！
From Kyun to Bakyun, happy birthday heart!
That was so high!
Things got really crazy, we're not too sure what happened!
We had so much fun that we're losing track of time!
But we still have one more...
One more very exciting thing to share with you!
We still have more surprises in store!
Maybe... a live? Can you guess what it is?
What could it be, what could it be?
FuwaMoco's 1st Anniversary!
We released a very, very special song for us, going to be Bau-Bau!
And then for our second anniversary, we were able to release life-sized outfit
our original song that's grown with us along this journey, a very special song.
And you know, singing and dancing is something that means so much to us. Yeah, music!
And Ruffians, you might have heard that you'd like to hear more from us too, right? Yeah! Yeah!
What do you think? Yeah!
Well, announcement is, come on, drum roll, okay, drum rolls, yes!
Done!
A new original song, yeah! So if you didn't watch it earlier,
and this song is extra special. It's written by none other than the legendary rock idol song composer
Matsukuma Kenta-san, who works with many series idol groups that we love!
Also with music for the idol group that Kuroda produces, Mami Shibuya no Taiko-san! Yeah!
But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay? So get ready.
Well, with this song, we like to express our lawless feelings as demon dogs.
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」ネオンの脇を抜け
"Partner, where shall we go?" Slipping past the neon lights,
バブルガムがはじけたら let's go
when the bubble gum pops, let's go.
最低な夜を潜って 僕は群れをなす
Slipping through the worst nights, we form a pack.
「あの頃よりもマシだね」 my way
"It's better than back then," my way.
「不完全なんです」首輪をつけた
"We're imperfect," wearing our collars.
良い子なんかもういや (ah)
We're done being good girls (ah)!
demon's residence 噛みついていけ この街は檻のようで
Demon's residence, bite back! This town is like a cage.
気分はどうだい 泣いているのかい 鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたんだ stray dogs
How are you feeling? Are you crying? Tearing off our chains, we kept screaming, stray dogs!
遥か彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を見上げるだけかい それでいいのかい? 燃えるなら ほら青く
Are you just going to look up at birds flying far away? Is that fine? If you're going to burn, burn blue!
「説教なんかいらない」スプレー缶振って
"We don't need lectures," shaking spray cans,
イタズラ書きで彩る runway
coloring the runway with graffiti.
愛情なんか coin toss 誰に bet するのか
Love is like a coin toss, who are you going to bet on?
不確定要素ばかりね lonely
Full of uncertain elements, lonely.
二人でひとつと決めた あの日を忘れない (ah)
We decided to be one together, we won't forget that day (ah)!
demon's residence 満天の空 あの星がひどく不快で 勝利はどうだい
Demon's residence, the starry sky. That star is so unpleasant, how is victory?
味覚がするのかい? 鎖を噛んで 吠えていたんだ stray dogs 僕ら
Does it taste like anything? Biting our chains, we howled, stray dogs, us!
宇宙さえも撃ち落して 見下ろす奈落 ビルは輝く lol, now i am free
Shooting down even the universe, looking down at the abyss, the buildings shine, lol, now I am free!
孤独を分け合い食べた
Sharing and eating our loneliness,
あの日を忘れない (ah) 夜を覗んだ stray dogs そうだ
we won't forget that day (ah)! Peering into the night, stray dogs, that's right!
怪物は世界の方さ 抜け出せるのかい 足は動くかい 走るなら今
The monsters are the ones in the world! Can you break out? Can your feet move? If you're going to run, now!
demon's residence stray dogs 僕ら この街を駆けて行け
Demon's residence, stray dogs, us, run through this town!
地獄の果てに何が見えるかい 鎖をちぎって 叫んでいたんだ stray dogs 僕ら
What can you see at the end of hell? Tearing off our chains, we kept screaming, stray dogs, us!
この街は檻のようで 君ならどうだい 共に駆けるかい? 夜明けが合図だ 行こう
This town is like a cage. How about you? Will you run with me? Dawn is the signal, let's go!
side by side
Finally we made it through
but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true
we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate
all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on it's the heart that we will follow
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow if you stay by my side
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories every day underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other now
we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been ruff times where nobody wanted us, we kept going, and we kept dreaming
Now we are here, we're not alone anymore
We'll be here together, we have smiles to protect, c'mon, let's go!
Dancing harmonies feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories every day underneath the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other now
we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Nya, nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
Nya, nya-nya-nya
nya-nya-nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
Nya, nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
Nya, nya-nya-nya
nya-nya-nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
Thank you for the encore, everyone!
That was "side by side"!
We really had side by side for you for the first live today!
初披露できてとっても... side by side...
Hatsuhilo dekite totte mo side by side...
This song made by Aiobahn-san, but also between...
FuwaMoco!
We know it's a song that you love a lot, but we also do because it's very special to us, since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about!
Nekopara! Nekopara!
And with this song, our dream of seeing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
そう、この曲でフワモコの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
Sou, kono kyoku de Fuwamoto no yume, bijo shojo gemu no shudaika o utau koto ga kanai mashita!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much for joining us for a special day again this year!
It's been a dream of years!
And you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you!
It's sad to say goodbye, but...
This next song is our last song.
But like all of them, it's a very special one.
You know, FUWAMOCO, as demon guard dogs, we're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that, and protect your smile, and do our aww is idol!
And just as I have fulfilled fuzzy and fuzis souls too.
We'll continue to be here with thousands and thousands of demon dog guards, all over remembering that, you know, every day isn't given.
Yeah, we don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down, we hope that you'll remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We'll cheer you on, Ruffians! So, please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today!
明日も
Tomorrow too,
明後日も
the day after tomorrow too,
あなたが笑っててますように ずっと... lala...
I hope you'll always be smiling... lala...
Thank you so much, Ruffians, for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song when everything's a lot, and know that we'll be here. This last song is for you.
Wishful Garnet!
過去を振り返ると思い出す ガーネットの空
Looking back at the past, I remember the garnet sky,
溢れてく光 この瞳に
overflowing light in these eyes.
映し出されたあの日は 美しく
That day reflected was so beautiful,
揺れる what do you think?
swaying... what do you think?
赤く滲んだ空に 願いました
I wished upon the red-tinged sky,
どうかこの願い 届けてください
Please, let this wish reach you.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow too, the day after tomorrow too,
あなたが笑っててますように
I hope you'll always be smiling.
離れ離れになっても 前を向けますように
Even if we're apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を わたしが壊してあげる
I will break the chains binding you.
もう負けないで 進むこと
Don't give up anymore, keep moving forward,
いつでもそばにいるから
because I'm always by your side.
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when you're feeling down or lose confidence,
目の前にいてくれる
you're right there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度となく救われた だから... so i love you
Saved countless times by your smile, so... so i love you
くじけそうになったら
Whenever you're about to give up,
手を伸ばして まだ知らない明日
reach out your hand and find a tomorrow we don't know yet
一緒に見つけよう
together.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow too, the day after tomorrow too,
あなたを照らしていたい
I want to keep shining upon you.
泣きそうになった時は こっち向いてほしい
When you look like you're going to cry, I want you to look this way.
世界でひとりぼっち そんな風に思わないで
Don't ever think you're all alone in this world.
愛してくれる人はきっと いつもあなたを想ってる
Surely, someone who loves you is always thinking of you.
いつもあなたを想ってる
Always thinking of you.
Wishful Garnet!
願いました どうかこの願い
I wished... Please, let this wish
届けてください
reach you!
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow too, the day after tomorrow too,
あなたが笑っててますように
I hope you'll always be smiling.
離れ離れになっても 前を向けますように
Even if we're apart, I hope you can look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を わたしが壊してあげる
I will break the chains binding you.
もう負けないで 進むこと
Don't give up anymore, keep moving forward,
輝く空へ
toward the shining sky!
明日も 明後日も あなたが笑っててますように
Tomorrow too, the day after tomorrow too, I hope you'll always be smiling.
離ればなれになっても 前を向けますように
Even if we are separated, may we look forward.
あなたを 縛る鎖を
The chains binding you...
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで 進むこと
Moving forward without losing anymore,
いつでもそばに あなたのそばに
Always by your side, by your side,
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I will always be there.
Bow wow!
Thank you so much for coming!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
Bow wow!